Hei!
Nu-mi vine să cred că voi fi
răpus de un glonț rătăcit...
Nu se poate să mori acum!
Cum rămâne cu visul tău?!
Spuneai că ești Sagara Yoshiharu?
Visul meu de a avea un castel,
o țară și multe femei...
Du-l tu la bun sfârșit pentru mine!
Ce tot spui acolo?
O poți face, Yoshiharu!
Așteaptă.
Nici măcar nu-ți știu numele!
Numele meu este
Kinoshita Toukichirou.
Toukichirou?
Tu ești Toyotomi Hideyoshi!
Nu muri!
Dacă mori acum,
istoria va fi dată peste cap!
Tu trebuie să-l servești pe
Nobunaga și să unificați Japonia!
Nobunaga?
Capul familiei Oda
este Oda... Nobuna.
Nu!
Ce se întâmplă?
Înțeleg. E un vis!
Sunt un mare fan al jocului
Ambiția lordului Oda Nobunaga
și cred că am adormit
în timp ce mă jucam.
O-O fată?
La naiba!
S-a zis cu tine.
Stop!
Nu poți răni o fată așa drăguță!
Ar fi așa o pierdere!
Și tu ești un soldat al familiei Oda?
Ce naiba cauți aici fără o armă?
La naiba.
Nu prea am gândit-o până la capăt.
Omoară-i o dată!
Am înțeles!
Trebuie să fac ceva.
Dacă nu...
I-Inamicul?
A downloadable extra for Lord Oba Nobunaga's Ambition:
„Strigăte-le de luptă!”
Are o întreagă armată
în acea cutie mică?
E-E cumva un vrăjitor?
Suprins?
În acest caz...
Am uitat să-l încarc!
Go! Kill them both!
Damn it!
Game over already?
But if I can protect her...
No! It's Onishibata!
Damn! We almost got Oda's general!
Withdraw!
Oda's general?
Are you unharmed?
I'm fine.
Keep pressing forward and rout the Imagawa.
And you...
Get off of me already!
How despicable for a mere foot soldier
to push down the head of the Oda family.
The head of the family is Oda Nobunaga.
Who's Nobunaga?
I'm the head of the Oda family,
Oda Nobuna!
Oda Nobuna no Yabou
Episode One
Nobuna and
the Monkey
Episode One
Nobuna and
the Monkey
Episode One
Nobuna and
the Monkey
Episode One
Nobuna and
the Monkey
Episode One
Nobuna and
the Monkey
Episode One
Nobuna and
the Monkey
This is the Sengoku Era.
The land is divided between powerful warlords,
who ceaselessly fight amongst themselves.
Any internal power struggle is an
invitation for your neighbors to attack.
Thus, it was decided that the firstborn child,
regardless of gender, would
become the head of the family.
The result of this was the birth
of the Princess Generals.
No way!
You're Katsuie?
Shibata
Katsuie
The fierce Shibata Katsuie.
Shibata
Katsuie
Her nickname is Riku.
Shibata
Katsuie
Do you have a problem with that?
N-No.
The Katsuie I know from my
games is a bearded old man.
Wh-What's wrong with you?
Stop staring at my breasts!
Uh, sorry.
They're just so big, so...
H-How impudent!
That's enough.
If nothing else, he saved my life.
I still can't believe Oda Nobunaga is a girl.
I understand that the strange
technique you used isn't magic.
Is it some kind of barbarian technology?
Technique?
Oh, the ringtone?
The battery died, so I can't use it anymore.
Aw.
And here I thought you
might be kind of interesting.
So?
You want to serve the Oda family?
Please, Lord Nobunaga, let—
What was that?!
You messed up the name of the
general you want to serve?!
Are you an idiot?!
I told you, my name is Nobuna!
So, what's your name?
Give me your name!
I hate the slow-witted!
Come on! Spit it out!
Sagara Yoshiharu!
Got it. It's Monkey.
It's Sagara Yoshiharu!
I'm from the future,
so I'm practically a god—
The future?!
I don't believe in gods or buddhas.
And no human would say something so weird.
That means you're a monkey.
Then, we can call him Monkey.
But if we're going to use him as a retainer, he'll need some sort of role.
Niwa
Nagahide
Niwa Nagahide.
Niwa
Nagahide
Her nickname is Manchiyo.
Niwa
Nagahide
The Oda family's tactician.
Niwa
Nagahide
You're right.
It felt good to step on him.
He can be in charge of my shoes.
That will do nicely.
Seventy points.
And why's that?!
I'm a monkey and in charge of your shoes?!
Does her calling me "Monkey" mean
I'm supposed to take his place?
The same name Nobunaga gave Toyotomi
Hideyoshi, the man who united Japan.
So, you failed to slay that idiot, Oda?
Imagawa
Yoshimoto
Imagawa Yoshimoto.
Imagawa
Yoshimoto
Ruler of the eastern coastal provinces,
Imagawa
Yoshimoto
and the countess closest to conquering Japan.
Imagawa
Yoshimoto
I-I'm terribly sorry.
We almost had her, and then, somebody interfered.
Matsudaira
Motoyasu
Matsudaira Motoyasu.
Matsudaira
Motoyasu
Later, she will become Tokugawa Ieyasu,
Matsudaira
Motoyasu
but currently, she is a mere
servant to the Imagawa family.
Matsudaira
Motoyasu
As punishment, I'll have
to cut your pay again!
Not that!
I'm already eating nothing but
potatoes four days a week.
Is that you, Hanzou?
The interference came from
a man the Oda call "Monkey."
So, she's taken in a monkey?
Nobuna is such a fool!
This is kind of shabby.
"Be grateful that you were
even given a place to stay,"
is what the princess says.
Maeda
Toshiie
Maeda Toshiie.
Maeda
Toshiie
Her nickname is Inuchiyo.
Maeda
Toshiie
The greatest spear wielder in the Oda clan.
Maeda
Toshiie
I was thrown into the Sengoku Era with nothing of my own,
so I can't really ask for much.
Is it not to your taste?
Old man Asano.
Oh, my. How valiant you look.
You look much like I did in my youth.
So much so that I wish you'd marry
my daughter Nene and take over my inn.
Introduce me!
Very well.
I'm Nene!
Nice to meet you, Mr. Monkey!
She's way too young! No, thanks!
You're a very noisy person, Mr. Monkey.
I'm not a monkey!
I'm Sagara Yoshiharu.
I understand, Mr. Monkey.
Whatever.
Intruder!
Damn.
Ow.
What's going on?
My name is Hachisuka Goemon.
I've come to serve you in
place of my master, Kinoshita.
Another little girl?
How rude.
I'm not good with long sentences.
Are you Toukichirou's daughter?
His companion!
He is the trunk, and I am
the vine hiding in its shade.
Together, we will make
our way in the world.
That was our promise.
So you can do, like, thirty or so letters, tops.
Sh-Shut up!
A promise you made with Tokichirou, huh?
With no idea of how to get home,
I'll have to survive here.
It sucks that it's not Nobunaga,
just some snippy little girl named Nobuna,
but saving a pretty girl and conquering Japan doesn't sound so bad.
Just wait, old man.
From now on, I'll live your dream!
Yoshitatsu plans on attacking Oda.
He's still young.
Saitou
Dousan
Saitou Dousan, the count of Mino.
Saitou
Dousan
A legend of the Sengoku Era,
Saitou
Dousan
who began as a merchant and
grew to rule an entire province.
Saitou
Dousan
Nobuhide, the Tiger of Owari Province, has died.
And the one who rose in his place...
...is a foolish girl with a taste for barbarian fashions.
Normally, she would make an excellent target.
Indeed. If you leave it to us and Yoshitatsu, we shall destroy her immediately.
I would take the opposite
approach, and befriend her.
Impossible!
To do what others would never consider.
That's what it takes to conquer the land.
The Viper of Mino Province
has requested an audience.
The Viper? You mean Saitou Dousan?!
Scripted event time!
But Mino Province is a rival of ours.
It's not surprising.
Wh-Why is that?
Because if I were going to ally with
somebody, it would be the Viper.
You didn't believe I was
from the future, did you?
And?
I'll prove it.
You'll be meeting with Saitou
Dousan at Shoutokuji Temple.
What are you talking about?
We haven't decided where
we're going to meet yet.
Reporting.
Mino Province just gave us the
location of the conference.
Wh-Where is it?
Shoutokuji Temple, I'm told.
Impossible.
What a surprise.
Ninety points.
Monkey, how did you know?
How much time do you think I spent playing the game Lord Oda Nobunaga's Ambition?
The meeting at Shoutokuji
is a mega-famous event in it.
M-Mega... eve...?
Is that some barbarian language?
The Monkey language.
You brought a lot of them.
500 riflemen. Pretty impressive, aren't they?
I brought them to show off to the Viper.
Come to think of it, Dousan sees
Nobunaga heading to the meeting, and...
If we kill Nobuna here,
Owari Province will belong
to the Saitou family.
Akechi
Mitsuhide
Akechi Juubei Mitsuhide, famous
for her literary and military talent.
Akechi
Mitsuhide
A young genius who has
begun to distinguish herself.
Akechi
Mitsuhide
Do you think it will be that easy?
Of course.
Everything is ready.
Hey, Nobuna!
You address your lord like that?
Whatever! Have your men light their rifles!
What if the rifles explode?
Are your men that inept?!
Of course not!
Don't underestimate us!
We've got trouble!
I-Impossible!
Impressive.
She had the rifles lit despite the
fact that they might explode.
She's either a complete fool, or...
She's late.
Lord Dousan, you really shouldn't dress
like that during an important meeting.
She'll do the same.
Making the other person feel at
ease is part of being a great leader.
So he was watching.
Anyway, that girl next to him is so cute!
I've kept you waiting, Viper.
What?!
No way!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why?
I mean, you're so beautiful.
Did I surprise you?
Well?
What the hell?!
She's stunning!
Why did you change your clothes?
I'm meeting the Viper of Mino.
It wouldn't be right to wear my usual clothes.
I see.
These two...
Dousan tried to make Nobuna feel at ease,
and Nobuna showed respect for Dousan.
You seem to have brought a lot of riflemen.
Now is the age of the rifle.
Many say they're barbarian toys.
Anyone foolish enough to say such a thing would
be downed in a single shot by my foot soldiers.
The Owari Province soldiers are
said to be the weakest in Japan,
but with rifles in their hands,
they're the strongest.
Someday, those rifles will destroy
the strongest cavalry of the
Sengoku Era: Takeda's cavalry!
Man, I'm so excited that I'm shaking!
After you've allied with me,
will you attack Suruga Province and Imagawa?
No. Mino.
Why focus on Mino Province?
The same reason you did, Viper.
The one who rules Mino
Province rules the nation.
It's the center of Japan,
dividing the east and west.
Build a well-constructed castle here,
and the nation is as good as yours.
To make a wealthy country,
where merchants travel freely.
That was your ambition, wasn't it?
So you know all about it?
I'm taking Mino Province.
Do you think I'll let you?
What if I told you that I will carry on your dream?
What?
I'll destroy the old systems that
have wrought havoc across Japan,
and turn this into a country that can
compete with the barbarian nations.
I've set my sights on the whole world!
You're a little brat,
but I'd be fine with you
conquering all of Japan!
So your gaze already lies beyond the sea?
Your ideals are correct.
But no one can follow you there.
The fact that they call
you a fool is proof of that.
Even so, I'll keep moving forward.
Destroying anything that gets in your way?
If you wish to start with Mino,
then I accept your challenge.
That's what I want.
Wait just a second!
You fool!
Do you want to be killed?!
Get back, Monkey!
Saitou Dousan!
I know what you're thinking!
You know what lies in store for Mino.
Stop being so stubborn!
What are you talking about?
This will be entertaining.
Let him speak.
Monkey...
It's fine.
Let me do this.
One wrong word and your
head will be lying on the floor.
Apologize, Monkey!
There's still time.
Dousan, when this meeting is
over, you'll tell your men this:
"My children shall tie their horses
at the gate of The Fool of Owari."
Wh-What?!
In other words, you already know
your son can't defeat Nobuna.
You know it can't happen!
Child, how did you know what I was thinking?
I just knew, is all.
What?
I'm from the future.
You're going to hand Mino over to Nobuna.
If you don't, your entire
life will have been a waste.
Saitou Dousan, Oda Nobuna is the only
one who can continue your dream!
Child...
I have completely lost.
Viper?
I didn't expect anyone from the future.
450 years in the future.
There, Saitou Dousan is a
hero of the Sengoku Era.
Is he?
I wrote my name in the
annals of history, then.
Thanks to you, the Viper has become
true to himself at the very end.
I will prepare a treaty handing Mino Province over to little miss Nobuna.
I will give Mino to my new daughter, Nobuna!
Really?
Thus, the Owari and Mino
Provinces formed an alliance.
Have you gone mad, Father?!
I refuse to accept it!
I guess I'll praise you for this.
It's thanks to you.
Say it to my face.
Shut up, already!
Just give me my shoes.
We're leaving!
Oh, these?
Why were you keeping them there?!
It's a misunderstanding!
I wouldn't want them to be
cold when you put them on!
You were getting off on the
smell of my feet, weren't you?
Nu am văzut niciodată
un asemenea pervers!
Simplul fapt că respiri
reprezintă un păcat.
Te voi ucide chiar acum!
Maimuță perversă!
Sper că ești pregătit!
tada jidai no mannaka tatasarete tomadou toki ni
When I, lost in time, was standing there confused
te wo hiite kureta hito e dekiru koto sagashita
You pulled me through, so I wanted to do something in return
kizutsuki nagara warau sugata
You were smiling even though you were being hurt
kokoro no ura namida ga mieta
I saw you shedding tears deep inside
sukui motomeru koe kikitoreru no wa
I could only understand your call for help
yurusareta mono dake
When you opened up to me
kazoe kirenu arashi wo koete
I will overcome the countless storms
anata no yami saku hikari ni naru
And become the light that cuts through your darkness
mou mayowanai tomo ni ikitai
I won't hesitate anymore; let's go together
chikau yume ga donna mubou de atte mo
No matter how unrealistic our ambitions are
oboeteite shinjirareru basho wa
Remember there's a place you can believe in
koko ni aru to
Right here
Episode Two
Oda Family
Power Struggles
Episode Two
Oda Family
Power Struggles
Episode Two
Oda Family
Power Struggles
Episode Two
Oda Family
Power Struggles
Episode Two
Oda Family
Power Struggles
Episode Two
Oda Family
Power Struggles